[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "And have you seen (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Well, sometimes if I have enough energy to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Does he feel that the emotions can all be kept in check?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, I don't want to speak for the president about Rick Santorum's comment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Finally, as we look at the forthcoming election and the battle hotting up, what do you identify now, given you're so closely involved with this campaign -- is there a slight credibility issue with his dramatic U-turn on the super PACs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Credibility issue -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "ORGAN: And let me just say that when the president is on the record of saying that these PACs are a threat to democracy, how can he have the brass neck to now support them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Exactly what I said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Is that how we are leaving things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Todd Smith"]}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "That ruins it a little bit, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "No you were christened James Todd Smith.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "What is -- what is a respectful way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "I think Todd works just fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "How are you feeling about the Grammy's?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "I feel great.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Grammy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Let's be honest -- winnings better than losing, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VB", "JJS", ":", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Without a doubt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "And I think just on a worldwide level, no democracy, you know, no democratic, you know, government is like just doling out all of the state secrets and all of the various nuances and dynamics that effect the decision making that goes on in the inner sanctum, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well let -- let me ask you a difficult question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Is America still the country of that opportunity do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Of course it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 211, "question": "I'm an Independent, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "What do -- by my mantra recently on the show --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "How do we keep America great?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "I think in order to keep America great, we have to keep America creative.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "And when you talk to people in that position, what do you say to them to inspire them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Look at me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ellen Griffith"]}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "When you look back, what was it about you that allowed you to get out of that trap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, there was this woman, her name was Ellen Griffith, and that was my grandmother and, you know, may she rest in peace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What do you do if you have no one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "You have to look at all the people in the world that are successful and you have synthesize all of those positions, those people, those goals they achieved, the things they did, the heroic moments.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sam Handle"]}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "You know someone in Belgium?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Before I got stuck with you, Sam Handle (ph) was an international brand.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Belgium"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Yes, right, kind of like guys who have one letter of the alphabet for a first name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Five years to the day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "What would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "That's harsh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ":"], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Chris Brown, Cold Play, Rihanna, Bruce Springsteen -- who do you get excited by?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "You know, I've got to tell you, you know, I grew up --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rihanna"], "PERSON": ["Chris Brown", "Bruce Springsteen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What have you learned about yourself through that process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Eat your soup, let her talk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Did you pick up on Jennifer then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "And you are living, walking proof that these shows, which often get derided by critics, really can actually produce world class stars, can't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "EX", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "What were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "You know, I had that little moment right there, very briefly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What was the moment for you when you realized that you were going to make it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Could you feel it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Now that I didn't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What was the moment when you knew it was going to be a smash and you and your career were never going to look back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Ooh, goodness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Do you sing like that in the bath?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Sometimes if I have enough energy to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Where does this lady rank?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "She really ranks right up there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What is like being Jennifer Hudson, with all of this nonsense being written about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "You know -- well, I try not to pay much attention to it, because you will go bonkers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer Hudson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Because that's what has always impressed me about you, is this inner strength that you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "First of all, I have to give credit to God and also my upbringing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Impending marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Definitely, definitely, every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What are the core values you think you got from your mother and your grandmother that you can take forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Oh my goodness, again, my faith in God, you know, family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Does he know this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arista Records"]}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What is the thinking behind it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "It started the year I started Arista Records.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tony Bennett"]}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Tantalize me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "I will tell you the show will open with Tony Bennett.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Greatest living crooner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "You know, I would say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Here is a question for you, and I have always wondered what your answer would be, if I could only allow you to listen to one song for the rest of your life, on repeat, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "First of all, it would be very painful, to listen to one song.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "When you look at what's happening with America now, what do you think the answer is to get America fired up again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I think it's going to have to be, A, an improved campaign.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}]